Vincent Pinas

Software developer / Student

http://30472.hosts1.ma-cloud.nl/portfolio/

Noord-Holland, Uithoorn (+31) 06 827 942 05

ikbengerrit92@gmail.com https://github.com/vincpinas

EXPERIENCE

CSU, Uithoorn—Intern

16-06-2020 - 03-07-2020

Worked with both hardware and software to repair desktops and laptops.

Unc Inc, Amsterdam — Intern

14-02-2022 - 15-07-2022

Worked as one of the main front-end developers on a project called KennisHub, this platform makes it easy for students, teachers and experts to connect and share knowledge with each other.

EDUCATION

Media College Amsterdam, Amsterdam — MBO

August 2020 - TODAY

Veenlanden College, Mijdrecht — MAVO

September 2015 - May 2019

PROJECTS

Kennishub - Online knowledge sharing platform

- Implemented React App to fetch, update and remove posts, topics and users through networking API using Redux.
- Implemented a responsive UI using SCSS.

Manga.lv - Online manga reader

- Designed and implemented React App that fetches manga through networking API.
- Implemented REST API in PHP for use in the front-end.

<u>TsChat</u> - Online Bidirectional communication using websockets.

- Designed and implemented a React frontend that makes use of websockets in TypeScript
- Created a backend using Socket.io and Express.js to share data between clients using websockets.

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

Photoshop / Adobe Html / Css(SCSS) JavaScript(TypeScript) Redux React.js / Node.js npm / git Php / Composer

SKILLS

Web Development Design

LANGUAGES

Dutch - Native level

Engels - Fluent level

ABOUT ME

Who am I?

My name is Vincent Pinas, I'm 19 years old, born in 2003 and I live in Noord-Holland.

Outside of school I like browsing online to explore all kinds of developments which is not only limited to software,

going to the gym and hanging out with friends.

What can I do for you?

Since I am aiming to become a front-end developer or a fullstack developer I currently mainly work with React.js, Node.js and PHP.

One example of what I made in React would be this entire portfolio.

I'd like to think I am an eager learner so I am happy to learn any new technologies to get something done.

My strengths.

I am quite a flexible person, I can usually adapt to my environment quite quickly and get in the flow. I like to be helpful so if you need anything you can ask me, as long as it's within my abilities of course.

Future goals.

I am currently aiming to perfect my knowledge of React and to start working more on backend solutions using Node.

While I'm making projects to work on those skills I will also be working on my planning skills.